It was supposed to be fun.
The Threesome is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Chad Hartigan.
Connor and his long-time crush Olivia engage in a threesome
with a sweet, alluring stranger named Jenny.
This encounter sparks a relationship between Connor and
Olivia, leading them to plan a life together.
However, their romance faces challenges when Jenny reappears, thrusting all three
into a difficult journey toward true accountability and adulthood.
Olivia Capitano, played by Zoey Deutch.
Connor, played by Jonah Hauer-King.
Jenny, played by Ruby Cruz.
Greg, played by Jaboukie Young-White.
Kevin, played by Josh Segarra.
Paul, played by Robert Longstreet.
The Threesome is a 2025 American romantic comedy drama film
starring Zoey Deutch, Jonah Hauer-King, and Ruby Cruz.
It is directed by Chad Hartigan and written by Ethan Ogilby.
The film had its world premiere at the South by Southwest Film & TV Festival on March 7,
2025, and was released in the United States on September 5, 2025, by Vertical.
The film explores themes of pregnancy, babysitter,
arkansas, wedding, gay marriage.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.